Good evening.King's Restaurant.
晚上好，国王饭店。
Good evening.I'm ringing about the job I understand you have vacant. Oh yes.
晚上好。我打电话是想询问你们那里的一个工作空缺。好的。
I'd like to find out a few more details,if i may.
恕我冒昧，我想多了解一些详情。
Yes,of course.Can i take your name? It's Peter Chin.
当然。我能问一下你的名字吗？彼得·陈。
Okay Peter.Well,if you want to ask about the job and then if we're both still interested, we could arrange for you to come for an interview.
好的，彼得。如果你想了解这份工作，并且之后我们双方仍感兴趣的话，我们可以安排你来面试。
Great,thanks.I'm afraid i missed the advert for the job but heard about it from a friend.
太好了，谢谢。恐怕我错过了招聘广告，但是我从一个朋友那里听说了。
That's no problem at all.What would you like to know?
完全没有关系。你想了解什么？
Well,um,what sort of work is it - washing up?
那是什么样的工作，洗碗吗？
It's answering the phone. Oh right,fine.
是接听电话。好的，很好。
And not waiting at table.
不能招待用餐。
That'd be good.And how many nights a week would it be?
很好。一周要工作几个晚上？
Well,we're really only busy at the weekend. So two nights?
我们只会在周末很忙。那么是两个晚上吗？
Three actually,so it would work out at twelve hours a week.
事实上是三个，所以一周要工作12个小时。
That'd be fine.It wouldn't interfere with my studies.
很好。这样就不会干扰我的学习了。
Are you at the university?
你在上大学吗？
Yes.First year Physics student. Oh.right.
是的，物理系一年级学生。好的。
Um,and because i'm not an EU national would i need a work permit?
因为我不属于欧盟国家，所以我需要一张工作许可吗？
Yes you would.Justget your tutor to sign it.
是的。让你的导师签字就行。
That wouldn't be a problem,if i were to get the job.Um,where exactly is the restaurant?
如果我能得到那份工作就没有问题。饭店具体在哪儿？
Well,we have two branches - the one we're recruiting for is in Hillsdunne Road.
我们有两家分支，我们招募的那家在Hillsdunne路。
I don't know that.How do you spell it please? It's H-I-double L-S-D-U-double N-E Road.
我不知道那里，请问怎么拼写？Hillsdunne路。
Got that.Thanks.is it near a bus stop?
记下了，谢谢。附近有公交车站吗？
Yes.The nearest one would probably be just beside the Library.
有。最近的一个可能就在图书馆旁边。
Oh yes,i know it.That'd be fine for me.And could i ask about the pay?
是的，我知道。对我来说很合适。我能问一下工资吗？
We're offering ￡4.45 an hour.
4.45英镑一小时。
That's very good.My last job was ￡3.95 an hour.
很好。我上一份工作是每小时3.95英镑。